Guide to the J. B. Matthews Papers, 1862-1986 and undated
J. B. Matthews papers 1862-1986 and undated
- Vertical Files Series, ca. 1920s-1980s Part I
  - Burton, Phillip, undated (Folder 15)
  - Busch, Roosevelt, 1950 (Folder 16)
  - Business Executives Move for Vietnam Peace, 1967-1970 (Folder 17)
  - Business Fights Communists in The Labor Movement, 1948 (Folder 18)
  - Businessman's Committee on Vietnam, 1965 (Folder 19)
  - Businessmen for Peace in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 20)
  - Businessmen's Educational Fund, 1970-1971 (Folder 21)
  - Butenko, John William, 1963 (Folder 22)
  - Butler, Edward, 1970 (Folder 23)
  - Butler, R., 1950 (Folder 24)
  - Buyers Strike Committee, 1946 (Folder 25)
  - Bykota Discussion Club, 1965 (Folder 26)
  - Cafeteria Employees Union, 1950 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Cahiers du Bolchevisme, 1927 (Folder 2)
  - Cain, Harry P., 1955-1957 (Folder 3)
  - California: Intelligence Bulletin, 1966-1967 (Folder 4)
  - The California Alliance for Peace, 1970 (Folder 5)
  - California Association for Supervision and Curriculum Development, 1960 (Folder 6)
  - California Committee for Fair Practices, 1961 (Folder 7)
  - California Democratic Council, 1958-1968 (Folder 8)
  - California Eagle, 1956 (Folder 9)
  - California Emergency Defense Committee, 1956 (Folder 10)
  - California Institute of Technology, 1948 (Folder 11)
  - California Labor Federation, AFL-CIO, 1960 (Folder 12)
  - California Labor School, 1946-1957 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  - California League for American Indians, 1958-1959 (Folder 2)
  - California Legislative Conference, undated (Folder 3)
  - California: Miscellaneous Schools, undated (Folder 4)
  - The California Quarterly, 1955-1957 (Folder 5)
  - California Rangers, 1965 (Folder 6)
  - California Teachers Association, 1961 (Folder 7)
  - The Californian, 1960-1961 (Folder 8)
  - Californians Against Capital Punishment, 1960 (Folder 9)
  - Californians for America, 1955 (Folder 10)
  - Californians for Liberal Representation, 1962-1969 (Folder 11)
  - Californians for New Politics, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Californians for The Bill of Rights, 1954-1958 (Folder 13)
  - The Call Association, Inc., 1949-1959 (Folder 14)
  - Calomiris, Angela.; FBI, 1950 (Folder 15)
  - Calypso Musical Enterprises, Ltd., 1947 (Folder 16)
  - Cambodia, 1971 (Folder 17)
  - Cambridge Community to End The War in Vietnam, 1965 (Folder 18)
  - Cambridge Nonviolent Action Committee, 1964 (Folder 19)
  - Cameo, 1964 (Box 75, Folder 1)
  - Cameron, Angus, 1955 (Folder 2)
  - Cameron and Kahn, Inc., 1958-1959 (Folder 3)
  - Cameron Associates, Inc., 1953-1960 (Folder 4)
  - Camp Calumet, 1959-1960 (Folder 5)
  - Camp Horizons, 1962-1963 (Folder 6)
  - Camp Rinderland, 1954-1970 (Folder 7)
  - Camp Lakeland, Inc., 1954-1959 (Folder 8)
  - Camp Madison-Felicia, Inc., 1958-1959 (Folder 9)
  - Camp Midvale, 1959-1966 (Folder 10)
  - Camp Summerlane, 1963 (Folder 11)
  - Camp Timberline, 1945-1955 (Folder 12)
  - Camp Unity, 1966 (Folder 13)
  - Camp Webatuck, 1963-1966 (Folder 14)
  - Camp WO-CHI-CA, undated (Folder 15)
  - Camp Woodland, 1954-1955 (Folder 16)
  - Campaign Expenditures Committee, 1947-1950 (Folder 17)
  - Campaign for Spanish Aid, 1938-1939 (Folder 18)
  - Campaign for World Government, 1948-1957 (Folder 19)
  - Campaign for Youth's Needs, undated (Folder 20)
  - Campaign to Check The Population Explosion, 1968-1969 (Folder 21)
  - Campus Americans for Democratic Action, 1966-1967(Formerly: Students for Democratic Action) (Folder 22)
  - Campus Concerned Democrats, 1968-1969& undated (Folder 23)
  - Campus Conservative Pack, 1972-1973 (Folder 24)
  - Campus Draft Opposition, 1968 (Folder 25)
  - Campus Sense, 1955 (Folder 26)
  - Canada, 1968-1969
    - General Papers, 1960-1972& undated (Box 75A, Folder 1-3)
    - Volumes, 1945-1971
  - The Canadian Far Eastern Newsletter, 1953-1958 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - The Canadian Tribune, 1957-1958 (Folder 2)
  - Canwell Committee, 1948-1949 (Folder 3)
  - Capitol Hill Organized Individuals for a Civilian Environment, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Captive Nations Committee--National, 1965-1966 (Folder 5)
  - Caravan of East and West, 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Cardinal Mindszenty Foundation, 1966-1973 (Folder 7)
  - Cards for Peace Trust, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Care, 1943-1952 (Folder 9)
  - Care of Children in Wartime, 1943 (Folder 10)
  - Carib, 1958-1960 (Folder 11-12)
  - Caribbean, 1961-1963 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - The Carnegie Endowment for International Peace, 1954-1958& undated (Folder 2-3)
  - The Carolina Israelite, 1953-1959 (Folder 4)
  - Carrie Chapman Catt Memorial Fund, Inc., 1954-1956 (Folder 5)
  - Cartan Travel Bureau, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Cartoonists & Illustrators School, undated (Folder 2)
  - Case Bill, 1946 (Folder 3)
  - Castle, Eugene, 1955 (Folder 4)
  - Catalyst, 1969 (Folder 5)
  - Catholic Church, undated (Folder 6)
  - Catholic Council on Civil Liberties, 19621?] (Folder 7)
  - The Catholic Peace Fellowship, 1965-1969 (Folder 8)
  - Catholic War Veterans, 1947-1954 (Folder 9)
  - The Catholic Worker Movement, 1956-1968 (Folder 10)
  - The Catonsville Nine Defense Committee, 1968-1969 (Folder 11)
  - Caucus to Constitute a National Organization of The Local Independent Anti-Vietnam-War Committees for The Withdrawal of U.S. Troops Now, 1965-1967 (Folder 12)
  - Caughlan, John, Defense Committee, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Cavalcade of Negro Art, undated (Folder 2)
  - Caw!, 1968-1969 (Folder 3)
  - Ce Soir, 1948 (Folder 4)
  - Center for Analysis of Public Issues, 1971 (Folder 5)
  - Center for Community Change, 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Center for Emergency Support, 1968-1969 (Folder 7)
  - Center for Marxist Education, 1969-1970 (Folder 8)
  - Center for New York City Affairs of The New School, 1969 (Folder 9)
  - The Center for Radical Research, 1967-1968 (Folder 10)
  - Center for The Study of Democratic Institutions, 1971 (Folder 11)
  - The Center Letter, 1969 (Folder 12)
  - Central America, 1954 (Folder 13)
  - Central America: Communism, 1954 (Folder 14)
  - Central Parcel Service, Inc., 1957-1958 (Folder 15)
  - Century Twenty One Limited, undated (Folder 16)
  - Cerf, Bennett, 1951-1953 (Folder 17)
  - Chalk Circle, 1966 (Folder 18)
  - Challenge, 1958 (Folder 19)
  - Challenge, 1962 (Folder 20)
  - Challenge, 1964-1968 (Folder 21)
  - The Challenge of Building Peace, 1969 (Folder 22)
  - Chamber of Commerce, 1946-1952 (Folder 23)
  - Champaign-Urbana Committee on The Yellen Case, 1961 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Champaign-Urbana Draft Resisters Union, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Chicago Council American-Soviet Relations, 1965-1970 (Folder 3)
  - China, 1953, 1968-1971& undated (Folder 4)
  - Christian Communist Movement, 1965 (Folder 5)
  - Christian Educational Association, 1955-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Christian Veteran Political Council, undated (Folder 7)
  - Christian Youth Corps, 1965 (Folder 8)
  - Christianity and Crisis, 1950-1969 (Folder 9)
  - Christoffel, Harold, 1941-1953 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Chrysler Corporation, 1942-1944 (Folder 2)
  - Chublarian, Rouben, undated (Folder 3)
  - Church, 1945-1950 (Folder 4)
  - Church League for Industrial Democracy, 1936-1957 (Folder 5)
  - The Church League of America
    - Papers, 1946, 1964-1971and undated (Folder 6)
    - The National Laymen's Digest, 1969-1972 (Folder 7)
    - News and Views, 1947-1972and undated (Folder 8-10)
  - Church of The Holy Trinity, 1948-1960 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Church of The United Nations, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Church Peace Mission, 1958-1962 (Folder 3)
  - The Church Peace Union See Box 111
  - Church World Service, undated (Folder 4)
  - The Churchman, 1948-1966& undated (Folder 5)
  - Cincinnati Citizens for Constitutional Liberties, 1961-1968 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Cincinnati Draft Project, 1968 (Folder 2)
  - Cinema Educational Guild, Inc., 1949-1966& undated (Folder 3)
  - Cinema 16, Inc., 1948-1949& undated (Folder 4)
  - Circuit Riders, Inc., 1934-1966& undated (Folder 5-7)
  - Citadel Press, 1957-1966 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Against Anti-Ballistic Missiles, 1969 (Folder 2)
  - Citizens Against Poverty, undated (Folder 3)
  - Citizens Against The ABM, 1969 (Folder 4)
  - Citizens Campaign Against Napalm, 1966-1967 (Folder 5)
  - Citizens Committee, 1948 (Folder 6)
  - Citizen's Committee Against The Trucks Law, 1953 (Folder 7)
  - Citizens Committee Against The War in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 8)
  - Citizens Committee for a Just Settlement of The Hospital Strike, 1959 (Folder 9)
  - Citizens Committee for a Nuclear Test Ban, 1963 (Folder 10)
  - Citizens Committee for African Freedom, 1964 (Folder 11)
  - Citizen's Committee for Amter, 1938 (Folder 12)
  - Citizen's Committee for Arts Projects, 1941 (Folder 13)
  - Citizens Committee for Constitutional Liberties (CCCL)
    - Papers, 1960-1962 (Box 84, Folder 14-15)
    - Papers, 1963-1971& undated (Box 85, Folder 1-3)
  - Citizens Committee for Hal Levin for Congress, 1966 (Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee for Harry Bridges, 1941 (Folder 5)
  - Citizens Committee for Julian Bond, 1966 (Folder 6)
  - Citizens Committee for McCarthy, 1948-1968 (Folder 7)
  - Citizens Committee for Mary Van Rleeck, undated (Folder 8)
  - Citizens Committee for Nuclear Disarmament, 1964 (Folder 9)
  - Citizens Committee for Peace with Freedom in Vietnam, undated (Folder 10)
  - Citizens Committee for Peace with Security, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Citizens Committee for Reciprocal World Trade, 1948 (Folder 12)
  - Citizens Committee for Robert Thompson [?] and Benjamin J. Davis, 1946 (Folder 13)
  - Citizens Committee for The Defense of Angelo Herndon, 1935 (Folder 14)
  - Citizens Committee for The Hoover Report, undated (Folder 15)
  - Citizens Committee for The Right to Keep and Bear Arms, undated (Folder 16)
  - Citizens Committee in Support of Maritime Workers, 1946 (Folder 17)
  - Citizens' Committee of Inquiry, 1964 (Folder 18)
  - Citizens' Committee of 100 on Transit, undated (Folder 19)
  - Citizens' Committee of Upper West Side, 1944-1946 (Folder 20)
  - Citizens Committee on Children of NYC, Inc., 1949 (Folder 21)
  - Citizens' Committee on Relief, undated (Box 86, Folder 1)
  - Citizens' Committee on Respect for Authority, undated (Folder 2)
  - Citizens' Committee to Defend Labor, 1947 (Folder 3)
  - Citizens Committee to Defend Representative Government, 1948 (Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee to Elect George Blake Charney, 1953 (Folder 5)
  - Citizens Committee to Free Earl Browder, 1942 (Folder 6-7)
  - Citizens Committee to Preserve American Freedoms, 1952-1966& undated (Box 87, Folder 1-4)
  - Citizens Committee to Re-Elect Peter V. Cacchione, undated (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - Citizens Committee to Safeguard The American Labor Party, undated (Folder 2)
  - Citizens Committee to Save Elysian Park for The People, 1965 (Folder 3)
  - Citizens Committee to Secure Bail for Martin Young, 1953 (Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee to Support The GE Strikers, 1969 (Folder 5)
  - Citizens Community Centers, Inc., 1969 (Folder 6)
  - Citizens Conference on International Economic Union, 1949 (Folder 7)
  - Citizens Coordinating Committee of El Paso, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Citizens's Council, 1972-1974 (Folder 9)
  - Citizens' Council on Civil and Political Education, 1965 (Folder 10)
  - Citizens Crusade Against Poverty, 1969 (Folder 11)
  - Citizen's Crusade for Voluntary Prayer, 1967 (Folder 12)
  - Citizens Emergency Committee, 1930 (Folder 13)
  - Citizens Emergency Conference for Interracial Unity, 1943 (Folder 14)
  - Citizens Emergency Defense Conference, 1952-1954 (Folder 15)
  - Citizens Exchange Corps, 1966-1974 (Folder 16)
  - Citizens for a New Prosperity, 1972& undated (Box 89, Folder 1)
  - Citizens for a Realistic Foreign Policy, 1964 (Folder 2)
  - Citizens for a Vote on Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 3)
  - Citizens for Constitutional Rights, 1961 (Folder 4)
  - Citizens for Constructive Education, 1972 (Folder 5)
  - Citizens for Decent Literature, 1972 (Folder 6)
  - Citizens for Dr. Thomas Matthew, 1969 (Folder 7)
  - Citizens for Farm Labor, 1964 (Folder 8)
  - Citizens for Humphrey, 1968 (Folder 9)
  - Citizens for Kennedy/Fulbright, 1967 (Folder 10)
  - Citizens for O'Dwyer, 1968 (Folder 11)
  - Citizens for Participation in Politics, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Citizens for Peace in Vietnam, 1967 (Folder 13)
  - Citizens for Victory, 1942 (Folder 14)
  - Citizens for Wallace, 1968[?] (Folder 15)
  - Citizens for Yes on Peace, 1967 (Folder 16)
  - Citizens Foreign Relations Committee, 1958 (Folder 17)
  - Citizens Legal Defense Alliance, 1970-1974 (Folder 18)
  - Citizens Legislative Conference of New York State, 1948 (Folder 19)
  - Citizens National Committee, Inc., 1946[?] (Folder 20)
  - Citizens Non-Partisan Committee for The Re-Election of Benjamin L. Davis to The City Council, 1945[?] (Folder 21)
  - Citizens Non-Partisan Committee to Elect a Negro for The State Senate, 1945 (Folder 22)
  - Citizens of Conscience of Washington Heights and Inwood, 1965 (Folder 23)
  - Citizens Planning and Housing Association, 1951 (Folder 24)
  - Citizens Revolt Against Pollution, 1969 (Folder 25)
  - Citizens Social Research Council, 1947-1948 (Folder 26)
  - Citizens to aid G.E. Strikers, 1970 (Folder 27)
  - Citizens Union, 1948-1961 (Folder 28)
  - Citizens United to Abolish The Wood-Rankin Committee, 1946 (Folder 29)
  - Citizens Victory Committee for Harry Bridges, undated (Folder 30)
  - City College of New York, 1950-1969 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - City Council of Youth, Cleveland, Ohio, undated (Folder 2)
  - City-Wide Citizens' Committee on Harlem, undated (Folder 3)
  - Civic Action Research and Education Project, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Civil Action Day Committee, 1967 (Folder 5)
  - Civil Affairs Austria, 1945-1948 (Folder 6)
  - The Civil Defense Letter Committee, 1961-1962 (Folder 7)
  - Civil Defense Protest Committee, 1960-1962 (Folder 8)
  - Civil Disobedience, 1965-1969 (Folder 9)
  - Civil Disorder Research Institute, 1969 (Folder 10)
  - Civil Liberties Council of Washington, 1948 (Folder 11)
  - Civil Liberties Educational Foundation, Inc., 1957-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Civil Liberties in American Colonies, 1933 (Folder 13)
  - Civil Liberties Legal Defense Fund, Inc., 1968-1969 (Folder 14)
  - Civil Liberties Union of Massachusetts, 1949 (Folder 15)
  - Civil Rights Defense Committee, 1941 (Folder 16)
  - Civil Rights Congress
    - Papers, 1944-1950 (Box 90, Folder 17-18)
    - Papers, 1951-1959& undated (Box 91, Folder 1-4)
  - Civil Rights Defense Committee, undated (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - Civil Rights Federation, 1938-1943 (Folder 2)
  - Civil Rights Legal Defense Fund, 1967 (Folder 3)
  - Civil Service, undated (Folder 4)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1947-1953 (Folder 5)
  - Civil Service Forum, 1946 (Folder 6)
  - Civilian Defense Volunteer Office (C.D.V.O.), 1942 (Folder 7)
  - Clarity, 1944, 1968& undated (Folder 8)
  - Clarity, 1940-1942 (Box 93, Folder 1-2)
  - Clark, John, 1948-1969 (Folder 3)
  - The Class Struggle, 1918-1919 (Folder 4)
  - Class Struggle, 1934-1935& undated (Folder 5)
  - Claude Lightfoot Defense Committee, 1954-1959 (Folder 6)
  - Claude Williams Committee, 1956-1971 (Folder 7)
  - Claudia Jones Defense Committee, undated (Folder 8)
  - Clay, Jane ( Goodbye America), 1963 (Folder 9)
  - Clements, John A.
    - Papers, 1947-1948 (Folder 10)
    - Papers, 1948-1963 (Box 94, Folder 1-5)
    - Papers, 1964-1965& undated (Box 95, Folder 1-3)
  - Clergy and Laymen Concerned about Vietnam, 1965-1970 (Folder 4-5)
  - Clergyman's Committee on China, Inc., 1969-1972 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Clergymen's Letter to FDR in Defense of Communist Party, 1940s[?] (Folder 2)
  - Cleveland Area Peace Action Council, 1968-1969 (Folder 3)
  - Cleveland Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1962 (Folder 4)
  - Cleveland Committee for Unemployment Insurance, 1931 (Folder 5)
  - Cleveland Committee to Abolish The House Un-American Activities Committee, 1948-1961 (Folder 6)
  - Cleveland Committee to End The War in Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Folder 7)
  - Cleveland Council on Anti-Semitism, 1969 (Folder 8)
  - Cleveland Council on World Affairs, 1957-1963 (Folder 9)
  - Cleveland Draft Resistance Union, 1968 (Folder 10)
  - Cleveland Free University, 1967 (Folder 11)
  - Cleveland: Now!, 1968 (Folder 12)
  - Cleveland Roman Cultural Association, 1966 (Folder 13)
  - Clevelanders for Constitutional Freedom, 1964 (Folder 14)
  - The Clipper, 1941 (Folder 15)
  - Closer Up, 1946-1963 (Folder 16-17)
  - Club Ulysses Young Fraternalists, 1942 (Folder 18)
  - Clubb, Oliver Edmund, 1951-1952 (Folder 19)
  - Coalition Against Racist Medical Care, 1970 (Folder 20)
  - Coalition Committee, 1948 (Folder 21)
  - Coalition for a Democratic Alternative, 1967-1968 (Folder 22)
  - Coalition for a Fair Ballot, 1970 (Folder 23)
  - Coalition for an Anti-Imperialist March, 1968 (Folder 24)
  - Coalition for an Anti-Imperialist Movement, 1968-1969 (Folder 25)
  - Coalition for an Independent Candidacy, 1968 (Folder 26)
  - Coalition for Community Action, undated (Folder 27)
  - Coalition for United Community Action, 1969 (Folder 28)
  - Coalition on National Priorities and Military Policy, 1969 (Folder 29)
  - Coastlines, 1956-1961 (Folder 30)
  - Collaboration with Other Communist Unions, 1950-1952 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Colorado College, 1948 (Folder 2)
  - Colorado Committee to Protect Civil Liberties, 1955-1962 (Folder 3)
  - Colorado State University, 1968 (Folder 4)
  - Columbia-Barnard Democratic Club, 1961 (Folder 5)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1946-1949 (Folder 6)
  - Columbia Pictures, 1951 (Folder 7)
  - Columbia University, 1947-1970 (Folder 8)
  - Columbia- FBI, 1946-1958 (Folder 9)
  - Columbus Conference, 1946 (Folder 10)
  - Combat, 1968-1972& undated (Folder 11)
  - Comicbooks, 1946 (Folder 12)
  - Cominform, 1947-1956 (Folder 13)
  - Comite Pro Democracia Espanola, undated (Folder 14)
  - Commentary, 1962& 1970 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Commerce Clearing House, Inc., 1951 (Folder 2)
  - Commercial Association, 1954 (Folder 3)
  - Commercial Telegraph Union, 1952-1953 (Folder 4)
  - Commission Internationale Pour l' aide aux Refugies Espagnols, undated (Folder 5)
  - Commission of Inquiry into The Charges Made Against Leon Trotsky in The Moscow Trials, 1937 (Folder 6)
  - Commission on Freedom of The Press, 1946 (Folder 7-8)
  - Commission on Social Action of Reform Judaism, 1957-1961 (Folder 9)
  - (VACANT) (Box 99)
- Vertical Files Series, ca. 1920s-1980s Part II
  - (VACANT) (Box 100)
  - Commission on World Peace, undated (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - Commission to Study The Organization of Peace, 1969 (Folder 2)
  - The Committee, 1964 (Folder 3)
  - Committee Against Academic Repression, 1969 (Folder 4)
  - Committee Against Barbarism in South Africa, undated (Folder 5)
  - Committee Against Nazism and Anti-Semitism, 1961-1965 (Folder 6)
  - Committee Against Nuclear Explosions, 1957-1959 (Folder 7)
  - Committee Against Nuclear Tests, 1960 (Folder 8)
  - Committee Against The Bomb, 1962 (Folder 9)
  - Committee Against The Ultra-Right, 1963 (Folder 10)
  - Committee for a Community Newspaper, 1963 (Folder 11)
  - Committee for a Democratic Far Eastern Policy (CDFEP)
    - General Papers, 1945-1949 (Folder 12-13)
    - General Papers, 1950-1963& undated (Box 102, Folder 1-4)
    - Publications and Periodicals:
      - Far East Reporter, ca. 1952 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Far East Spotlight (Vol. IV, No. 1 - Vol. VI, No. 3), 1948-1950 (Folder 2)
      - Far East Spotlight (Leaflets and Pamphlets), 1952& undated (Folder 3)
      - Information Bulletin and its successor, Spotlight on The Far East, 1946-1948 (Folder 4)
  - Committee for a Democratic Policy Toward China, undated (Folder 5)
  - Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1961-1970 (Folder 6)
  - Committee for a Free China, undated (Folder 7)
  - Committee for a Just Peace in Mid-East, 1970 (Folder 8)
  - Committee for a Just Peace with Italy, 1947 (Folder 9)
  - Committee for a Voluntary Census, 1970 (Folder 10)
  - Committee for a Winter Confrontation with Congress, 1968 (Folder 11)
  - Committee for Academic Freedom in Tampa, 1960-1961 (Folder 12)
  - Committee for Action on The Georgia Lynchings, undated (Folder 13)
  - Committee for African Students, 1961 (Folder 14)
  - Committee for American Rights, 1955 (Folder 15)
  - Committee for an American Medical Brigade, 1967 (Folder 16)
  - Committee for an Effective Congress, 1971 (Folder 17)
  - Committee for an Independent Socialist Magazine, 1953 (Folder 18)
  - Committee for April 24, 1962 (Folder 19)
  - Committee for Boycott Against Japanese Aggression, 1938 (Folder 20)
  - Committee for Citizenship Rights, 1942 (Folder 21)
  - Committee for Community Action Against Poverty and Delinquency, 1964 (Folder 22)
  - Committee for Concerted Peace Efforts, 1938 (Folder 23)
  - Committee for Conscientious Objectors, 1967 (Folder 24)
  - Committee for Conservative Action, 1970-1971 (Folder 25)
  - Committee for Constitutional Freedom, 1961 (Folder 26)
  - Committee for Constitutional Government, 1951 (Folder 27)
  - Committee for Constitutional Liberties, 1961-1962 (Folder 28)
  - Committee for Cooperation with The Japan Council Against The A and H Bombs, 1961 (Folder 29)
  - Committee for Defense Against Terrorist Attacks, 1970 (Folder 30)
  - Committee for Defense of Public Education, 1941& undated (Folder 31)
  - Committee for Democracy and Intellectual Freedom, 1939 (Folder 32)
  - Committee for Democratic Decent Unionism, 1947 (Box 104, Folder 1)
  - Committee for Democratic Rights, undated (Folder 2)
  - Committee for Democratic Rights in The U.S.A., 1962 (Folder 3)
  - Committee for Direct Action, 1967 (Folder 4)
  - Committee for Draft Resistance, 1967-1968 (Folder 5)
  - Committee for Barter Peace Witness, 1961 (Folder 6)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1952 (Folder 7)
  - Committee for Equal Justice for Mrs. Recy Taylor, 1945 (Folder 8)
  - Committee for Fair Selection of Draft Board Members, 1968 (Folder 9)
  - Committee for Fifth Avenue Vietnam Peace Parade, undated (Folder 10)
  - Committee for Foreign Policy Alternatives, 1965 (Folder 11)
  - Committee for Free Inquiry, 1966 (Folder 12)
  - Committee for Free Political Advocacy, 1949 (Folder 13)
  - Committee for Freedom of Conscience, 1958 (Folder 14)
  - Committee for Freedom of The Press, 1955 (Folder 15)
  - Committee for Fulfillment of The American Dream, 1968 (Folder 16)
  - Committee for German Relief Entertainment, undated (Folder 17)
  - Committee for G.I. Rights, 1968 (Folder 18)
  - Committee for Guild Unity, undated (Folder 19)
  - Committee for Health Care of The Aged, 1962 (Folder 20)
  - Committee for Health in California, 1961-1962 (Folder 21)
  - Committee for Hollywood on Trial, 1948-1968 (Folder 22)
  - Committee for Howard Levy, 1968 (Folder 23)
  - Committee for Independent Political Action, 1965-1966 (Folder 24)
  - Committee for Independent Political Action on The West Side, 1965-1968 (Folder 25)
  - Committee for International Friendly Visits, 1967 (Folder 26)
  - Committee for International Peace Action, 1963-1964 (Folder 27)
  - Committee for Jewish Writers and Artists, 1943 (Folder 28)
  - Committee for Legal Assistance in The South, 1964-1965 (Folder 29)
  - The Committee for Leo Roch, 1961[?] (Folder 30)
  - Committee for Maritime Unity, 1946 (Folder 31)
  - Committee for May Day, 1948 (Folder 32)
  - Committee for Medical Aid to Victims of U.S. Bombings, undated (Folder 33)
  - Committee for Medical Freedom, undated (Folder 34)
  - Committee for Miners, 1963-1965 (Folder 35)
  - Committee for Nonviolent Action (CNVA)
    - Papers, 1957-1961 (Box 105, Folder 1-4)
    - Papers, 1962-1966,June (Box 106, Folder 1-5)
    - Papers, 1966, July - 1969& undated (Box 107, Folder 1-3)
  - Committee for North Carolina, 1946& undated (Folder 4)
  - Committee for Nuclear Weapons Development, 1959 (Folder 5)